https://www.adassoc.org.uk/aa-privacy-policy/

Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
The Advertising Association promotes the role and rights of responsible advertising and its value to people, society, businesses and the economy. We represent UK advertisers, agencies and brands on behalf of the entire industry, acting as the connection between industry professionals and the politicians and policy-makers.
Resource
Ad Pays Series
Advertising's Big Questions
Adspend Figures
Advertising Matters
Annual Review
Media Smart
Cannes Lions
Our Team
Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
The Advertising Association focuses on major industry and policy areas that have huge ramifications on UK advertising. This section contains our work around Brexit, HFSS and gambling advertising, data and e-privacy, trust, the digital charter and our Industrial Strategy campaigns.
Our Work
Current Work Streams
Advertising and the Economy
Brexit and Trade Policy
Children and Young People
Climate Action
Consultation Responses
Coronavirus
See All Of Our Work
Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
Credos is the advertising industry’s independent think tank. It produces research, evidence and reports into the impact and effectiveness of and public and political response to advertising on behalf of UK advertisers in order to enable the industry to make informed decisions.
Credos
Ad Pays Series
Ad PAYS 8: UK advertising's social contr...
AD PAYS 7: UK ADVERTISING'S DIGITAL REVO...
Advertising Pays 6: World class talent, ...
Advertising Pays: How advertising fuels ...
Ad Pays 5: How advertising fuels the Sco...
Advertising's Big Questions
Is advertising a barrier to market entry...
How does advertising affect innovation, ...
Does advertising increase consumer price...
Does advertising grow markets?
How does advertising work?
Representation in Advertising
The whole picture: How advertising portr...
Pretty As A Picture
Picture of Health?
See More On Credos
Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
Front Foot is our industry’s member network of over 50 businesses across UK advertising. It aims to promote the role of responsible advertising and its value to people, society and the economy through a coalition of senior leaders from advertisers, agencies and media owners.
Front Foot
Front Foot Members
Front Foot in Action
Front Foot News
Become A Member
Members Testimonials
Become A Member
Membership offers a range of exclusive benefits, from early access to Credos research to invitations to exclusive networking events. The Front Foot network helps us shape the annual agenda and means members are at the forefront of the latest thinking and industry initiatives of value to their businesses.
See All
Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
We run a number of events throughout the year, from our annual LEAD summit to the Media Business Course and regular breakfast briefings for our members. We are also the official UK representative for the world’s biggest festival of creativity – Cannes Lions.
All events
15.12.20:Tackling Public Trust in Advertising
16.12.20:Ad Net Zero: COP26 Briefing With Strategy Director, Charles Ogilvie
28.01.21:RESET 2021
21.06.21:Cannes Lions
02.11.21:Media Business Course 2021
28
Jan
AA Event, All events
RESET 2021
Online event
See All
Have you read our latest Advertising Pays report?
Search
Our Organisation Representing UK Advertising
The Advertising Association promotes the role and rights of responsible advertising and its value to people, society, businesses and the economy. We represent UK advertisers, agencies and brands on behalf of the entire industry, acting as the connection between industry professionals and the politicians and policy-makers.
Resource
Ad Pays Series
Advertising's Big Questions
Adspend Figures
Advertising Matters
Annual Review
Media Smart
Cannes Lions
Our Work Current Work Streams
The Advertising Association focuses on major industry and policy areas that have huge ramifications on UK advertising. This section contains our work around Brexit, HFSS and gambling advertising, data and e-privacy, trust, the digital charter and our Industrial Strategy campaigns.
See All Of Our Work
Our Work
Current Work Streams
Advertising and the Economy
Brexit and Trade Policy
Children and Young People
Climate Action
Consultation Responses
Credos UK Advertising's Think Tank
Credos is the advertising industry’s independent think tank. It produces research, evidence and reports into the impact and effectiveness of and public and political response to advertising on behalf of UK advertisers in order to enable the industry to make informed decisions.
See More On Credos
Credos
Ad Pays Series
Ad PAYS 8: UK advertising's social contr...
AD PAYS 7: UK ADVERTISING'S DIGITAL REVO...
Advertising Pays 6: World class talent, ...
Advertising Pays: How advertising fuels ...
Ad Pays 5: How advertising fuels the Sco...
Advertising's Big Questions
Is advertising a barrier to market entry...
How does advertising affect innovation, ...
Does advertising increase consumer price...
Does advertising grow markets?
How does advertising work?
Representation in Advertising
The whole picture: How advertising portr...
Pretty As A Picture
Picture of Health?
Front Foot Our Industry Network
Front Foot is our industry’s member network of over 50 businesses across UK advertising. It aims to promote the role of responsible advertising and its value to people, society and the economy through a coalition of senior leaders from advertisers, agencies and media owners.
See All
Front Foot
Front Foot Members
Front Foot in Action
Front Foot News
Become A Member
Members Testimonials
Become A Member
Membership offers a range of exclusive benefits, from early access to Credos research to invitations to exclusive networking events. The Front Foot network helps us shape the annual agenda and means members are at the forefront of the latest thinking and industry initiatives of value to their businesses.
Events Dates for your diary
We run a number of events throughout the year, from our annual LEAD summit to the Media Business Course and regular breakfast briefings for our members. We are also the official UK representative for the world’s biggest festival of creativity – Cannes Lions.
See All
All events
15.12.20:Tackling Public Trust in Advertising
16.12.20:Ad Net Zero: COP26 Briefing With Strategy Director, Charles Ogilvie
28.01.21:RESET 2021
21.06.21:Cannes Lions
02.11.21:Media Business Course 2021
17
Jun
AA Event, All events
Cannes Lions
Cannes, France
Search
2
Privacy Policy
/ June 21st 2017
Advertising Association Privacy Policy
How to contact us
If you have any questions about privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.
Email us at: aa@adassoc.org.uk
Or write to us at: Advertising Association, 12 Henrietta St, Covent Garden, London, WC2E 8LH
What data do we collect?
The type of personal data that we collect and use depends on the relationship you have with the Advertising Association, why you are interacting with us and the type of services or products you want us to provide to you. This data may include, for example:
personal identification information, such as name, email address, phone number, organisation, job title;
contact details, such as work or mailing address;
attendance of Advertising Association events;
any other personal data we may obtain through you interacting with us
How do we collect your data?
You directly provide us with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:
become a member of the Advertising Association
become a member of Front Foot
register for newsletters on our website
send us enquiries
book on and attend our events, courses and other activities
voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback via email
use or view our website via your browser’s cookies
otherwise provide us with personal data
The Advertising Association may also receive your data indirectly from the following sources:
Trade association members
How will we use your data?
The Advertising Association collects your data so that we can:
Email you with newsletters and events.
Send member value reports
Publish research papers
The Advertising Association will share your data with our sister organisations.
Credos
Media Smart UK
Front Foot
How do we look after your data?
We have put in place appropriate security measures to help prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have also put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.
What are your data protection rights?
We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:
The right to access – You have the right to request for copies of your personal data. Depending on the amount of effort required we may charge you a small fee for this service.
The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete information you believe is incomplete.
The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to us processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organisation, or directly to you, under certain conditions.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
Cookies
For information about how we use cookies, please see our separate cookie policy.
Privacy policies of other websites
The Advertising Association website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
The Advertising Association keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page.
This privacy policy was last updated on 28 May 2019.
How to contact the appropriate authority
Should you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that the Advertising Association has not addressed your concern in a satisfactory manner, please contact us here in the first instance. However, you may contact the Information Commissioner’s Office at any time.
About Us
Our Work
Memberships
Events
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Cookie Policy
Cookie Settings
© 2020 Advertising Association. Registered in England no 211587 V.A.T. Reg No GB238 5402 64
